人人影视
YYeTs.com
原创翻译  双语字幕
■
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
翻译：Iz    红豆包    奈奈良
校对：Iz          总监   IZ
时间轴：今        后期：吉吉
《开心汉堡店》
第三季第十九集
鲍勃  我们要错过电影的开场了
Bob, we're gonna miss the beginning of the movie.
而且我裤子里还藏着巧克力呢
Plus, I'm smuggling chocolate in my pants.
别等到那儿都化了
We got to get there before it melts.
马上就好  再等一下
I'm gonna get it. Just a sec.
能把后面的车窗摇下来吗
Ugh! Can you roll down the windows back here?
我都闻到蒂娜的口气了
I'm starting to breathe in Tina's breath.
不能  坏掉了
I can't. They're broken.
我今天早上是不是忘记刷牙了
I think I forgot to brush this morning. Did I?
是的  是的  你的确没刷
Yeah. Yeah, you did.
猜猜我是谁
Hey, who am I?
我是鲍勃的汽车
I'm Bob's car!
真有你的  JP[吉米名字的首字母]
Good one, J.P.
不好笑  吉米
Uh, not a good one, Jimmy.
启动了
Started right up.
他们进屋了  老爸
They went inside, Dad.
赶紧开车  吉恩脱鞋了
Start driving! Gene just took off his shoes!
还脱了袜子
And my socks!
你们就不能把你们的孩子都洗干净了吗
Why don't you wash your children?
这下可好了
Oh, great.
带家人看场破电影要这么难吗
Can't I just take my family to a stupid movie?
3D版《狗狗舞会》才不是破电影
Dog Prom 3D is not a stupid movie!
我们就这样把车扔下可以吗
Are we gonna just leave our car there like that?
等爸妈不行的那天我们也这么做
That's what we're gonna do when Dad and Mom break down.
把他们扔在路边
Leave them by the side of the road!
伙计们  你们想看现场电视节目录制吗
Hey, guys, you want to see a live TV show taping?
-什么东西  -给我看看
- Do I! - Give me that.
"邀您参加《全家游戏王》节目录制"
"Come to a taping of Family Fracas."
《全家游戏王》是啥
What's Family Fracas?
是一档竞技节目  先让两家人
It's a game show where they make families do weird stuff
做奇怪的游戏  再往他们身上倒泡沫
and then dump foam all over them.
我喜欢奇怪游戏和泡沫  我们去吧
I'm into weird stuff and foam. Can we go?
我们应该回家叫拖车
We should go home and call a tow truck.
车自己不会长腿跑掉  鲍鲍
The car's not going anywhere, Bobby.
去吧  肯定有意思
Come on, it'll be fun.
求你了  老爸
Please, Dad?
-求你了  老爸  -去吧
- Please, Dad! - Come on!
-去吧  去吧  去吧  -求你了
- Come on, come on. Come on. - Please!
13频道
看哪  是《帕姆法庭》
Oh, look! Pam's Court!
我很喜欢她敲木槌的样子  砰
I love the way she bangs that gavel. Bang!
那不是帕姆的前夫查克吗
Hey, isn't that Pam's ex-husband Chuck?
天哪
Oh, my God.
他在这里干嘛
What's he doing here?
你好  查克
Oh, hey, Chuck.
你们好  贝尔彻一家
Hello, Belchers.
好久不见
Long time no see
我还记得你上次害我节目被砍又被炒鱿鱼
since you got my show canceled and me fired.
咪咪  咪咪  咪咪  咪
A boobity boobity boobity boo!
琳达  很高兴再见到穿着衣服的你
Linda, nice to see you dressed again.
谢谢
Thank you.
对哦  那次很抱歉...
Yeah. Sorry about that. It...
都是过去的事了  鲍勃
Water under the bridge, Bob.
-很好  -不堪回首的
- Oh, good. - Dark, dirty water.
如恶梦般的过去
Under a horrible bridge.
但现在都没关系了
Oh, but all is well now.
我现在是《全家游戏王》的新主持人
You're looking at the new host of Family Fracas!
查克  我们有麻烦了
Chuck, we got a problem.
摩根家庭退出节目了
The Morgan family just dropped out of the show.
食物中毒  真恶心
Food poisoning. Gross!
我们得在十分钟内另找一个五人组的家庭
We got to find another family of five in the next ten minutes.
那怎么可能
But how the heck are we gonna do that?
这儿就有现成的
The heck right here.
没错  我们就是五人家庭组
Yeah! We're a family of five.
我们不是  一  二  三  四
No, we're not. One, two, three, four.
对  我们是五个人
Oh, yes we are!
哈利  别找他们
Harry, this is a bad idea.
有总比没有强
No idea's a bad idea.
我喜欢这个人
I like this guy!
我  我说不好
I... I don't know.
特等奖是一辆全新的休旅车
Grand prize is a brand-new minivan.
老爸  这还用想吗
Dad, this is a no-brainer.
-老爸  拜托  -不行  不行
- Dad, come on! - No, no. No, no, no.
鲍鲍  如果我们赢了
Bobby! If we win the minivan,
就能解救那辆休旅车于水深火热中
we can put the car out of its misery.
-不要  -不管了  我们参加
No. What the hell. Let's do it!
不行  -太好了
No! - Fantastic!
为《全家游戏王》节目欢呼吧
Hooray for Family Fracas!
欢迎来到《全家游戏王》
It's time for Family Fracas!
我是你们的主持人  查克・查尔斯
Here's your host... Chuck Charles!
大家好
Hiya, folks!
哇  那不是鲍勃吗
Whoa. Is that Bob?
让我们欢迎卫冕冠军  奥唐奈家庭
Let's welcome back the reigning champs, the O'Donnell family!
与奥唐奈家庭展开竞争的是贝尔彻一家
And competing against the O'Donnells are the Belchers.
-你们好  -你好  琳达
- Hi! - Hi, Linda.
看  蒂娜上《家庭游戏王》了
Look. Tina's on Family Fracas.
我堂兄本来也要上这个节目的
My cousin was gonna be on that show,
但他不想穿那套衣服  我能理解他
but he didn't want to wear that outfit. I don't blame him.
贝尔彻  介绍一下你的家人
Belchers, introduce yourselves.
我是鲍勃  这是我的妻子琳达
Uh, well, I'm Bob, and this is my wife Linda.
别看我头发
Don't look at my hair.
我没想到今天会上电视
I didn't know I was gonna be on TV.
这是我的女儿露易丝
And this is my daughter Louise.
我是露易丝  我会赢的
It's Louise!  And she is gonna win.
好了  好了  可以了  那位
Okay, okay, okeydoke. And that one.
那是吉恩
That's Gene.
摄影机  你今天可以休息了
Camera, take the day off!
据说镜头里的人看起来会比本人胖十磅
我已经自己胖了十磅
I added ten pounds to myself!
最后那位是蒂娜
And the last one's Tina.
你们好  我是蒂娜
Hi. I'm Tina.
我喜欢马  音乐还有男孩
I like horses, music and boys.
你们好  男孩们  我是蒂娜
Hi, boys. I'm Tina.
好了  说得够多了
Okay, that's more than enough.
好了  我们开始比赛吧
All right, let's get Frackin'!
接下来是"绞尽脑汁"环节
It's time for the Brain Drain!
这两个人好像弄丢了他们的弹球
Well, it looks like these guys have lost their marbles.
此处为双关  "lose one's marbles" 也有"失去理智  发疯"的意思
率先用球装满各自大脑的组获胜
The first team to fill their brain with these wins the challenge.
而迎接失败组的是什么呢
And what does the other team get?
泡沫
Foamed!
没错  泡沫
That's right... foamed.
各就各位  预备  开始
On your mark, get set, go!
你握我的手是想让我分心吗
Are you trying to distract me by holding my hand?
-啥  -欧文  我也有那种感觉
- Huh, what? - Owen, I feel it, too.
但目前  我们是竞争对手
But right now, we're competitors.
在赢你之前我不能爱上你
I can't be sweet on you before I beat on you.
蒂娜  赶紧填弹球
Tina, marble me!
对哦
Oh, right.
搞定
Done!
泡沫摄像机拍摄
我吃进去了  我吃进去了
I ate it! I ate it!
味道不错
Num, num, num. I like it!
率先从汤中舀出全部苍蝇的小组赢得本轮
First team to remove all the flies from their soup wins.
失败组会得到  一脸的泡沫
Losing team gets... face full of foam!
老妈  准备好了没  兴奋起来了没
All right, Mom, you ready? You pumped?
那是当然
Yeah!
-煽我的脸  -啥
- Slap my face! - What?
煽啊
Slap it!
那我煽你的脸
I'll slap yours.
我兴奋了  我兴奋了
Oh, uh, I'm pumped! I'm pumped!
开  始
And... go!
搞定
Done!
-耶  -倒泡沫
- Yeah! - Foam time!
贝尔彻和奥唐奈家庭打了个平局
The Belchers and the O'Donnells are tied.
在"真人夹娃娃"环节胜出的组
Whoever wins the Human Claw challenge
将赢得整场比赛
wins the whole game.
休旅车已是我们囊中之物了
I can smell that minivan.
-前排座位是我的  -我要第三排
- I call shotgun! - I call optional third row.
整个第三排都是我的
The whole third row.
孩子们  闭嘴  闭嘴  闭嘴
Children, shut up, shut up, shut up!
鲍勃和帕特将被钢丝吊着
And Bob and Pat are gonna get dunked
进入球池中
into a pit full of blue balls.
最先找到黄球的人获胜
The first one to find a yellow ball wins.
但是他们得用嘴把球衔出来
But they have to grab the ball with their teeth.
其他人控制钢丝
Families, you control the crane.
控制不好就赢不了比赛  我说得对吗
No crane, no gain, am I right?
英语中有句谚语叫"No pains, no gains"  意为"无劳不获"
正确
I am right!
我腹股沟这边的
My harness is a little tight
-安全带有点紧  -开始
- around the groin... - Go!
加油  老爸  让我们为你骄傲一次吧
Come on, Dad! Make us proud for once!
我找到了  我找到了
I got one! I got one!
老爸赢了
Dad won!
用砖头砸我脑袋吧
Well, bash my head in with a brick.
贝尔彻家居然赢了
The Belchers won.
我们赢了  我们赢了
We won! We won!
-耶  -太好了
- Yes! Yay! - All right!
耶  鲍鲍
Yay, Bobby!
哇塞  蒂娜赢了
Wow, Tina won.
叭叭叭
Honk, honk, honk!
奥唐奈一家  很遗憾你们要离开了
O'Donnells, we are really sorry to see you go.
你们是好人
You are good people.
再见了  乔伊和欧文
Bye, Joey and Owen!
你们虽然输了  但表现得不错
You're leaving in shame, but you played a good game.
他们烂毙了
They were terrible.
现在这个奖品转盘将决定
And now the Belchers are gonna spin the prize wheel
贝尔彻一家能否把全新的休旅车开回家
for a chance to win a brand-new minivan!
我来转
I got this.
拜托  拜托  拜托  休旅车
Come on, come on, come on, minivan.
一桶五加仑的全家泡沫
Oh, hey, a five-gallon bucket of Fracas foam,
这样你们就能在家里玩泡沫了
so you can get foamed at home.
在家玩  不要
Home foam! No!
太好了  相信我  味道不错
Yes! It tastes good. Trust me.
贝尔彻家庭将于明天以冠军身份回归
The Belchers will return tomorrow as the champs
对休旅车再次发起冲击
and have another shot at the minivan.
我们还会回来的
Hey! We're coming back!
我正是这个意思
That's exactly what I just said.
为冠军家庭鼓掌吧
Put your hands together for the winning family!
你们听到了吗
You hear that?
我们是冠军家庭
We're the winning family!
是的  他们都听到了  我有麦克风
Yes, they all hear that! I have a microphone.
向《全家游戏王》史上
Congratulations to the most annoying
最烦人冠军家庭表示祝贺
winning family in Fracas history.
我们赢得了最烦人家庭  耶
We won most annoying! Yeah!
我上电视了  妈
Hi, Ma!
这真是比休旅车强一万倍啊
You guys, this is so much better than the minivan.
吉恩  别再吃那玩意儿了
Gene, stop eating that crap.
我知道你是嫉妒我拉肚子能拉出泡沫
You're just jealous that I have frothy diarrhea.
来啊  你这大蠢蛋
Come on, you big idiot.
吉米  你昨晚看《全家游戏王》了吗
Hey, Jimmy, did you happen to catch Family Fracas last night?
我们上节目了  还赢了比赛
'Cause we were on it, and we won.
就是那个最可悲家庭获得冠军的节目吗
Oh yeah, is that the show where the most pathetic family wins?
不  不  不  不是那样的  吉米
No, no. No, it isn't, Jimmy.
你今晚看看吧  我会在电视上喊你的
Why don't you watch it tonight? I'll send you a shout out.
是吗  你先看看我这个吧
Oh, yeah, why don't you watch this?
我是鲍勃  我上电视节目了
Hey, I'm Bob! I'm on a game show! Blah, blah, blah!
我  我不想看  我要用我手里的
I... I don't want to watch that. I'm gonna change the channel
遥控器换频道  我换
with my remote that I have. Click!
-还是鲍勃  还是  -等等  我换
- I'm still Bob, and I'm still on... - Wait, wait, wait. Click.
-这个台  -我刚刚把你关了  关了
- this channel. - I just shut you off! I just shut you off...
-还是我  -你不能说话了
- And I'm on that. - So you can't say anything!
-现在我在"关了频道"  -我关了你
- Now I'm on shut off channel. - I shut you off!
贝尔彻一家
Belchers,
来见见你们的竞争对手  张一家
meet your competition... the Changs.
希望大家今晚和张家的男生玩得开心
Hey. Everybody Chang sons tonight.
英国新浪潮乐队Wang Chung于1986年发行的单曲"Everybody have fun tonight"曾获美国公告牌第二位
天哪
Oh, dear lord.
天呀  是帕姆
Oh, my gosh, there's Pam!
你好  帕姆  不对  法官大人
Hi, Pam! I mean, Your Honor.
查克  你又和这些好人们一起合作了呢
Chuck. I see you're working with these nice folks again.
真为你高兴
How fun for you!
我得上法庭了
Well, I have to get to court.
你不是真的法官
You're not a real judge.
如果有人找我  请去内庭
If anyone needs me, I'll be in my chambers.
那不是内庭  那只是化妆室
It's not chambers. It's a dressing room!
我判你亲我的屁股  看见这没
I sentence you to kiss my ass! See this right here?
-那就是你的惩罚  -你不是...
- That's your punishment! - Oh, wouldn't you... ?
-这正合你意吧  -你亲啊
- Oh, you would love it. - You can just kiss it.
亲就亲  谁怕谁
Oh, I will do it.
你们要亲就赶快亲吧  我快崩溃了
Somebody better kiss somebody's ass, or I'm gonna go crazy.
贝尔彻家和张家打平了
Belchers and Changs are tied.
赢得"真人夹娃娃"环节的家庭
Whoever wins the Human Claw
将会成为今晚的赢家
takes the game.
祝你们好运  张家  贝尔彻家也是
Good luck, Changs! And Belchers.
但更多好运还是给张家
But mostly Changs.
开始
And go!
老爸  快把那球衔出来
Yeah, Dad, grab those balls!
我衔到了
I got one!
真遗憾  乔
Oh! So sorry, Joe.
鲍勃用他的狗鼻子先找到了球
Bob's little rat snout found the ball first,
贝尔彻家获胜
which means the Belchers win!
好耶
All right!
你刚才说我是狗鼻子么
Did you just say rat snout?
我来转轮盘
Let me at that wheel!
停下  停下  停下
Stay! Stay! Stay! Stay! Stay!
又是泡沫
Foam again?!
查克  我能冲某人喊个话吗
Uh, Chuck, can I give someone a shout out?
当然不能
Absolutely not.
吉米・派丝多是个傻蛋  说完了
Jimmy Pesto's an idiot! The end.
真粗鲁啊
Tough shout out. Hmm.
谢谢分享  鲍勃
Thanks for sharing, Bob.
真高兴你们还能继续比赛
So glad you guys are coming back.
我能不能给餐厅打个广告  开心...
If I could just mention my restaurant, Bob's...
不能
No, you may not.
*披萨大战*
*Pizza game*
*口水大战*
*Talking trash*
*转动轮盘*
*spinning the wheel*
*全家泡沫*
*Fracas foam*
*带回家吧*
*Get foamed at home*
*吉米・派丝多*
*There's Jimmy Pesto*
*他要气疯了*
*He's so mad*
*全家泡沫  带回家吧*
*Fracas foam, get foamed at home*
*把吉米气疯*
*Jimmy's so mad*
*休旅车不能给你了*
*No minivan for you.*
哈利  求你了  把贝尔彻一家弄走吧
Harry, please, please, please kick the Belchers off the show.
你这话都说了一星期了
You've asked me that every night this week.
-我怎么告诉你的  -你说
- And what do I say? - You say,
"瞧好了"  然后你手就晃来晃去的
"Watch this," And then, you do that thing with your hands.
没错  查克  瞧好了
That's right, Chuck. Watch this.
更熟练了哦
Oh, oh, rounder.
-接下来呢  -反方向继续
- Whoa! Where we going? - Opposites.
-伸手  -你就是这么敷衍我的
- Here comes a hand. - Ah, that's how you get me!
你说过他们就来一集
You said they could be on one episode,
可他们来了一次又一次
but they keep coming back again and again.
这是我们的工作
Look, it's part of the job.
理查德・道森还在亲过
Richard Dawson used to
理查德・道森  美国竞技类电视节目《家庭问答》的前主持人
《家庭问答》里的所有女性呢
kiss all the women on Family Feud.
他可没挑三拣四  不过是撅起嘴唇而已
He didn't pick and choose. He just puckered up.
撅起嘴唇来  查克
Pucker up, Chuck.
我说真的呢  撅起嘴唇来
No, seriously, pucker up.
过来  跟我练习
Okay, come here. Practice on me.
-我是道森  你是我  -好吧
- I'm Dawson, you're me. - Okay.
-你是道森  我还是我  -好的
- You're Dawson, I'm me. - Okay.
-对  就像刚才那样  -好的
- Yeah, just like that. - Okay.
这回我们都是道森  两个道森
Now we're both Dawson. Double Dawson.
好了
Okay.
-可以了吗  -再一次
- Okay, are we good? - One more.
既然露易丝一直转到泡沫
Maybe someone else should spin the prize wheel tonight
今晚或许该换个人转
since Louise keeps landing on foam.
我还以为你就想要5大桶泡沫呢
Ooh! I thought you wanted five big buckets of foam!
-我不想  -你怎么不早说  蒂娜
- No. - I wish you would have told me sooner, Tina!
别担心  我们会还会一直赢的
Don't worry. We'll beat the other family like we always do.
今晚能把休旅车领回家  我有预感
And tonight, we win the van. I feel it.
你有没有预感到你屁股就要开花了
You're gonna feel your butt being spanked.
你的预感该这样才是
That's what you're gonna feel.
吉米  你要参加《全家游戏王》吗
Jimmy?! You're on Family Fracas?
没错  我报了名  做好输的准备吧
Yup. I signed us up. Get ready to lose.
我只看到四个派丝多家的人
I only count four Pestos
另一个是你的酒保崔佛
and your bartender Trev.
我告诉他们他才是我一直想要的孩子
I told them he was the son I always wanted.
-什么  -说得对  老爸
- What? - Right on, Pops. Ha!
你们已经见过了是吧
Oh, I see you guys have met.
吉米  现在走还来得及
Jimmy, you should just leave right now,
你们打不过我们的
because we're unbeatable.
吉米・派丝多
Jimmy Pesto!
直播时被鲍勃骂傻蛋的人就是你啊
Oh, you're the guy Bob called an idiot on the air.
就算是吧
Yeah, yeah, whatever.
你讨厌鲍勃  我也讨厌  我喜欢你
Hmm. You hate Bob, I hate Bob. I like you.
小吉米  我们是朋友
Jimmy Jr., you and I are friends
甚至曾经一度超越朋友关系
and have been more than friends on one and a half occasions.
如果你非要这么说
If you say so.
不过今晚  我们是对手
But tonight, we're competitors.
我必须把对你的感情放一边
I have to put aside my feelings for you.
还要毁掉你
And destroy you.
你搞得气氛太紧张了  蒂娜
Whoa. You're being kind of intense, Tina.
我知道  我故意的
I know. I bring it.
好  开始
And... go!
吉恩  蒂娜  加油刷
Come on Gene and Tina! Brush!
画圈圈  画圈圈
Tiny circles! Tiny circles!
加油啊  小吉
Come on, Jay Ju!
真不敢相信我被你逼得看这种节目  快
I can't believe you made me care about this. Come on!
加油  吉米  快
Do it, Jimmy! Go!
小吉米  你有地方没刷到
Hey, Jimmy Jr., you missed a spot.
-在你脸上  -够了  蒂娜
- On your face. - Quit it, Tina!
蒂  速度
T! Pick up the pace!
快刷  快刷  快刷
Brush, brush, brush, brush!
完成
Done!
该死
Damn it!
你打到我眼睛了
You hit my eye!
我也来  我们又是双胞胎了
Here. Now we're twins again!
-完成  -太棒了
- Done! - Yes!
让你们互相扔个蛋都扔不好
Oh, what's the point of having twins if they can't
要双胞胎有何用
hit each other with eggs like they were supposed to?
贝尔彻和派丝多打成了平手
The Belchers and Pestos are neck and neck.
在"真人夹娃娃"环节结束前
It's anybody's game
谁都可能是赢家
as we head into the Human Claw!
准备好认输吧  吉米
Have fun losing, Jimmy.
说得好  吉米
Well said, Jimmy.
预备  去找球吧
Ready, set, grab that ball!
-冠军产生了  -啥
- We have a winner! - Huh?
不
No!
刚刚怎么回事
What just happened?
我们输给派丝多家了
We lost to the Pestos.
我们做得不错了
We had a good run.
这话可出自一个讨厌跑步的小孩之口哦
And that's from a kid who hates running.
习语"have a good run[干得不错]"中"run"一词又意为"跑步"
抱歉  鲍勃
I'm so sorry, Bob.
派丝多一家成为《全家游戏王》的新冠军
The Pestos are the new champs of Family Fracas!
能把我降下来了吗
Uh, can you lower me down now?
我们在努力了
We're trying!
卡住了  鲍鲍
It's stuck, Bobby!
查克  钢丝绳卡住了
Chuck, the crane is stuck.
鲍勃  等一下
Bob, just a second.
派丝多家赢得了一辆全新的休旅车
And the Pestos win a brand-new minivan!
太好了
Oh, yeah! Oh, yeah!
-使劲拉  -孩子们  停下
- Pull! - Kids, stop.
别拉了  停下
Don't do that. Stop!
不要不要
No, no, no!
-天哪  -老爸
- Oh, boy. - Oh, Dad.
太糟糕了
Oh, that's too bad.
我们跟贝尔彻家来个隆重的招牌式告别吧
Let's give the Belchers a big Family Fracas bye-bye!
拜拜了  贝尔彻
Bye-bye, Belchers!
拜  咋了  我告个别而已
Bye! What? I'm saying good-bye.
我知道你们在想什么
I know what you're all thinking...
我们不仅输给了派丝多
not only did we lose to the Pestos
我还丢了那么大的人
but I also humiliated myself.
没错  我就是这么想的
Correct. I was thinking that.
好吧  你说的对  我搞砸了
Well, you're right. I blew it.
至少我们还有这些蠢毙了的泡沫
At least we have all this stupid foam.
鲍鲍  我要把这些泡沫都处理了
Aw, Bobby. I'm gonna get rid of this Fracas foam.
我要全倒进马桶冲走  永别了
I'm gonna flush it down the toilet. Bye.
不要  你不能这么做
No! You can't!
他说的对  这上面写不能倒马桶
It's true. It says right there you can't.
老爸  想听点好消息不
Hey, Dad, want a little good news?
你要火了
You're about to go viral.
停下
Stop!
《全家游戏王》掉裤子哥
太糟糕了
Oh, that's too bad.
他的裤子看一次掉一次
His pants come off every time.
我真谢谢你们这么一遍遍地提醒我
Thanks a lot, guys. Thanks for helping me get past this.
不用见外
No problem.
吉米怎么可能两秒内就找到球了
How did Jimmy find that ball in two seconds?
根本不可能啊
It's almost impossible.
鲍勃  别折磨自己了
Bob, stop obsessing.
都过去了
It's over.
这是他第五次绕街道遛弯了
This is the fifth time he's circled the block.
吉米  我知道了  你赢了休旅车
Jimmy, I get it. You won the minivan.
接受吧  鲍勃  你注定要输
Face it, Bob. You were destined to lose.
我知道  查克肯定也知道
I knew it, Chuck sure knew it.
啥  什么叫"查克肯定也知道"
Wh... what do you mean, "Chuck sure knew it"?
你什么意思
What does that mean?
什么  没什么意思  你知道的
What? Nothing. I... I have a disease
我一直有乱说话的毛病  先走了
where I say things, you know, and it makes me drive away...
冠军...
We have a w...
老爸  如果你倒退着看的话
Dad, if you watch the video in reverse
裤子就能穿上了
your pants go back on.
谢了  露易丝  我是在看吉米
Thanks, Louise. I'm just watching Jimmy.
他好像完全知道黄球的位置
It's like he knew exactly where to find the yellow ball.
我有种感觉  是查克告诉他球在哪儿的
And I have a hunch Chuck told him where to look.
看
Watch.
-冠军  -看见没
- We... - Did you see that?
看见了  等等  你要我看什么
Yeah. Wait, what was I supposed to see?
他根本就没找  他作弊了
He barely fished for it. He cheated.
我们被骗了
We were wronged.
听着  我们家是在很多方面都很逊
Look, there are a lot of things this family's terrible at.
那确实
That's true.
但我们在《全家游戏王》上绝对是高手
We were really good at Family Fracas.
就算输  我也要输得心服口服
And if we're gonna lose, I want to lose fair and square.
我可不想输给那个作弊的蠢货
Not because that jerk Pesto cheated.
老爸  能暂停一下吗 我们要迟到了
Hey, Dad, can we put a pin in this? We're running late.
你们要去哪儿
For what?
去坐派丝多家的休旅车
For the Pesto's minivan.
小吉米要在车里放《情迷哈瓦那》
Jimmy Jr.'s having a screening of Dirty Dancing: Havana Nights.
2004年上映的美国爱情片
啥  不  你们没听到我刚才说什么吗
What? No! Didn't you hear what I just said?
那是作弊得来的休旅车
That's the van of a cheater!
我们能做啥呢  老爸  坐这看视频吗
What are we supposed to do, Dad? Watch the TV here?
-我看得都想吐了  -知道我要干嘛吗
- That thing makes me sick! - You know what I'm gonna do?
我要开车去演播厅
I'm gonna drive down to the studio...
车坏了  老爸
The car's broken, Dad!
妈的  那我就走着去
Damn it! I'm gonna walk to the studio
然后跟那群人当面对质
and talk to those people face-to-face!
你  你  你不行
You, you, not you
-还有你  -蒂娜  你在这干嘛
- and you. - Tina, what are you doing here?
我们来看电影了
We're here for the screening.
对  让我们上去  快点
Yeah, let us in. Let's do this. Come on.
可是蒂娜  你昨天在《全家游戏王》
I don't know, Tina. You said some pretty mean things
说了很难听的话
on Family Fracas yesterday.
爆米花我们就笑纳了
We'll take that popcorn though.
-谢谢你  -小吉米  等等
- Thank you. - Jimmy Jr., wait!
你之前看到的是我比赛的面孔
What you saw before was my game face.
这才是我正常的面孔
This is my normal face.
让我们上车  小心我往你尾气管塞香蕉
Let us in! Oh, you're getting a banana in your tailpipe.
我可不是在说你的车
And I am not talking about the van.
我觉得吉米・派丝多在
I think Jimmy Pesto cheated
-"人体夹娃娃"环节作弊了  -是吗
- at the Human Claw game. - Hmm. You do?
没错  而且我觉得查克是帮凶
Yes, and I... I think Chuck might've helped him.
这是啥意思
Um, what's happening right now?
是这样鲍勃  我相信你相信自己被骗了
Here's the thing, Bob. I believe you believe you were wronged.
-我该说谢谢么  -这可是大新闻
- Thank you? - This is big.
-是的  -我还可以把它搞得更大
- Yes. - And I could make it a lot bigger.
是的  等下  你什么意思
Yes! Wait, what do you mean?
我是说在《帕姆法庭》上
I'm talking about Bob versus Chuck
来一场鲍勃查克对质
on Pam's Court.
不要  我不想那样
Um, no. I don't want to do that.
我觉得我应该去真正的有律师的法庭
How 'bout I just go to a real court with real lawyers?
那可要花不少钱  你没钱
That costs serious dough. You don't have it.
你怎么知道我没钱
What makes you say that?
你衣服上的污渍  你身上的气味
Those stains, your smells,
你没开车  你的孩子
you walked here, your children,
你没戴珠宝首饰
you're not wearing any jewelry.
靠  好吧  《帕姆法庭》
Aw, crap. All right, Pam's Court.
-就这么定了  -很好
- Let's do it. - All right!
恭喜你  鲍勃
Congratulations, Bob.
贝尔彻一家重回荧幕啦
The Belchers are back on TV!
你知道和这句话押韵的是什么吗
You know what that rhymes with?
长岛冰茶
Long Island Iced Tea.
我要来一杯
I'm gonna have one.
你办公桌后居然有个吧台
You have a bar in your desk?
你办公桌后没有吧台么
You don't have a bar in your desk?
那我就不打搅你了
I'm gonna leave you alone.
谢谢
Thank you.
-肃静  -这里是帕姆法官的审判现场
- Order. - This is the courtroom of Judge Pam.
-反对无效  -帕姆法官一锤定音
- I'll allow it. - And Judge Pam has the final word.
罪名成立  无罪释放
Guilty. Not guilty.
咱们法庭上见
We'll see you in court.
帕姆法官的法庭
Judge Pam's court.
我判你不得转台
I sentence you to stay tuned.
今天的《帕姆法庭》很特别
In a very special episode of Pam's Court,
汉堡兄鲍勃・贝尔彻控诉吉米・派丝多
burger man Bob Belcher is suing Jimmy Pesto
和身为《全家游戏王》主持人
and Pam's ex-husband and new host of Family Fracas,
同时也是帕姆前夫的查克 Chales
Chuck Charles.
本案被称为"愤怒的大球"案件
This is the case of the Great Balls of Ire.
"Great Balls of Ire" 美国摇滚歌手Jerry Lee Lewis于1957年录制的大热单曲
全体起立  帕姆法庭现在开庭
All rise. Pam's Court is now in session.
请就座  终于有除了我以外的第二个人
You may be seated. So, someone else besides me
指控查克作弊了
is accusing Chuck of cheating.
"cheat" 有"作弊"和"外遇"的意思
贝尔彻先生  你说
Mr. Belcher, you claim
查克在《全家游戏王》中
that Chuck helped Jimmy Pesto
帮吉米・派丝多作弊了
cheat at Family Fracas.
是的法官大人  在"人体夹娃娃"环节
Uh, yes, Your Honor. At the Human Claw game,
那是我最擅长的环节
which I happen to be pretty good at.
你有证据证明你说的话吗
Do you have any evidence to support your claim?
我有  法官  吉米说  以下为引用
Uh, yes, I do, Your Honor. Jimmy said Chuck, quote,
"查克肯定知道我会输"
"Sure knew I was gonna lose."
我想请问  查克怎么会知道呢
Now, I ask the court, how was Chuck so sure?
派丝多先生  你说这话了吗
Mr. Pesto, did you say this?
我说了
Yeah. I said it.
他承认了
So he admits it!
是的  我承认你输了
Yeah, I admit that you lost.
没人会惊讶
And no one was surprised.
法官大人  原告很明显没有证据
Your Honor, the prosecution clearly has no case.
我不想赞成被告
I hate to agree with the defense,
我恨被告
and also, I hate the defense
恨他那张自命不凡的脸
and his smug face,
和他长得畸形的小弟弟
and his misshapen penis.
在座听审的人可是很喜欢
Ho-ho-ho-ho! Well, it pleased the court.
那是他们装出来的
The court was faking it.
我可不这样认为
I don't think so.
-你给我闭嘴  -不  你闭嘴
- You shut up. - No, you shut up.
-闭嘴  -闭嘴
- Shut your mouth. - Shut your mouth.
-要我过去帮你闭吗  -这段剪掉
I will jump over there, and shut it for you. - Edit that out.
你还有别的证据吗  贝尔彻先生
Do you have any other evidence, Mr. Belcher?
他当然有  你有的  对吧
You bet he does! You got something, right?
-快交出来  -其实  我没有了
- Come on, give it to 'em. - Actually, I... I don't.
我  我以为
I... I... thought, uh...
我说了那个之后
that when I said that one thing
他就会自己坦白的
he would just confess.
鲍鲍  就只有这个吗
Bobby, that's all you got?
快  我们传秘密证人
Quick! Let's call a surprise witness!
谁
Who?
亨利・基辛格  原美国国家安全顾问  国务卿
我请求传唤亨利・基辛格
I call Henry Kissinger to the stand!
肃静  我有裁决结果了
Order! I think I have my ruling.
鲍勃能胜诉吗
Will Bob's beef be settled?
广告之后告诉你
Lettuce find out after the break.
鲍勃  我们要输了
Bob, we're gonna lose this case.
吉米作弊了  琳  我确定
Jimmy cheated, Lin. I know it.
看  我们上电视了
Hey, we're on TV.
知道  蒂娜  这是《帕姆法庭》
We know, Tina. We're on Pam's Court.
很酷是吧  是电视节目哦
Pretty neat, huh? It's a TV show.
不  我是说那台电视  嗨
No, we're on that TV. Hi.
-等等  有了  -啥
- Wait a sec. That's it! - What?
准备开拍  三  二
And we're back in three, two...
我去内庭仔细回顾了本案
I went to my chambers and reviewed this case.
反对  你并没有
Objection! You did not!
你一直在这儿
You were here.
你一直在补妆
You were putting on makeup the whole time.
你不化妆也很美  亲爱的
You don't even need makeup, hon.
-谢谢  -美呆了
- Oh, thank you. - You're beautiful.
-那袍子  -你太好了
- And that robe... - You're wonderful.
不过说真的我还真想看看你素颜的样子
I'd love to see you without makeup though to be honest.
审判继续
Moving on!
在"愤怒的大球"一案中  我宣判
In the case of Great Balls of Ire, I rule that...
等等  法官大人
Wait, Your Honor!
我有别的证据了  我有证据了
I... I have new evidence. I can prove my case.
-你说吧  -这些摄像机一直在工作吧
- Go on. - These cameras, they're always rolling. Right?
-没错  -也就是说
- Correct. - A... and the same with the cameras
拍《全家游戏王》的摄像机也是一样咯
on Family Fracas, right?
某台摄像机
One of those cameras
可能拍到了查克帮吉米作弊的画面
may have caught Chuck helping Jimmy cheat.
泡沫摄像机
The Foam Cam!
老爸  泡沫摄像机装在天花板上
Dad, the Foam Cam is on the ceiling!
给我东西吃的摄像机我是不会忘的
I never forget a camera that feeds me.
反对  反对
Objection! Objection!
道听途说  不可信  道听途说
Hearsay! Inadmissible... hears-say...
反对无效
Overruled!
给我调泡沫摄像机的带子
Bring me the Foam Cam tape.
我们是不是要赢了
Does this mean we're gonna win?
-但愿如此  蒂娜  -太好了
- I sure hope so, Tina. - Good.
你死定了  胜利是属于我们的
Your ass is grass. And I'm gonna mow it.
别烦我
Leave me alone!
我们
Hey, so we...
不能放那卷带子
can't show that tape.
看来你真的帮吉米作弊了
Oh, you did help Jimmy cheat.
是的  是的  我得让贝尔彻一家出局
Yes. Yes! And I had to get rid of the Belchers.
是你逼我的
You gave me no choice.
我把球直接放进了吉米嘴里
I put the ball in Jimmy's mouth.
你把球放进了自己嘴里
You put it in your mouth
然后在跟他接吻的时候传到了他嘴里
and then you kissed it into his mouth.
啥  我没有
What? No.
我用手放进他嘴里的
I put it into his mouth with my hand.
倒是也可以这么做
Huh. That's one way to do it.
给我吧
I'll take that.
证据来了  白痴
Ha! There's the evidence, idiot.
你才是白痴
Ha, you're the idiot.
我们怎么办
What do we do?
我是不会让我一个节目的主持人
I'm not gonna let the host of one of my shows
在我的另一个节目上吃败仗的
lose a trial on another one of my shows.
-你这是做什么  -不好意思
- Hey! What are you doing? - Whoops.
帕姆法官  你看到了吗
Ah, Judge Pam, did you see that?
啥  看啥
Huh? See what?
我看到了
I saw it!
证据肯定在那卷带子上
The evidence must be on that tape.
-也就是说老爸是对的  -没错
- Which means Dad was right. - Yes!
我的打火机这是怎么了
What is going on with my lighter right now?
它怎么把这卷带子点燃了
It's burning this tape.
搞什么  他在烧那卷带子
What the hell? He's burning the tape!
帕姆  你知道该怎么做吧
Pam? You know what to do.
好吧
Right.
由于没有实物证据
Without any actual evidence,
我宣布被告无罪
I have to rule in favor of the defense.
-好耶  -太好了  这才是正义
- Yes! - Oh, yeah! Justice!
这是怎么回事
What's going on?
我们为什么还要被淋泡沫
Why are we getting foamed?
这不是法庭节目吗
This is a court show.
《帕姆法庭》的输家也要被淋泡沫
The losers get foamed on Pam's Court.
太荒谬了
That's insane.
这个频道的所有节目都有泡沫
They have foam on all their shows on this channel.
我不同意
Oh, no friggin' way!
给我休旅车
I want my minivan!
你给我坐下
All right, you're gonna have to sit down.
坐下吧
Down you go.
我会踢你下巴的
I will kick you in the jaw.
-我会  -我就这样用手扼住你的喉
- I will... - Just put my hand on your throat,
坐下吧
and down you go.
我们现在怎么办
What're we gonna do now?
凉拌  我们输了
Nothing. We lost.
-可吉米和查克作弊了  -不重要了
- But Jimmy and Chuck cheated. - Doesn't matter.
我们永远也赢不了的
We were never gonna win this case.
他们都设计好了
This whole thing was fixed.
我们回家吧
Let's just go home and...
以后绝不再看13频道的节目了
and never watch any shows on Channel 13 again!
-别这样  你不是真心的  -我是
- Oh come on, you don't mean that. - Yes I do!
我也许还是会看一点点《帕姆法庭》
I might watch a little bit of Pam's Court.
就一点点
Just a little bit.
我们的车啥时候才能修好  老爸
When are we getting the car back, Dad?
我不知道
I don't know.
昨天修理师给我打电话了
The mechanic called yesterday
但我没回
but I never called him back.
我以为我们肯定能赢到休旅车呢
I thought we were gonna win the minivan.
那车对我来说已经死了
That van is dead to me!
看  就在那儿呢
Look, there it is.
我好喜欢哦
Oh, I love it so much.
车出问题了么  吉米
Oh, problem with the van, Jimmy?
啥  没什么  该死
What? It's nothing. Damn it!
原来你不会换轮胎
You don't know how to change a tire. Ha!
你才不会换轮胎
You don't know how to change a tire.
猜猜我是谁  我不会换轮胎
Hey. Who am I? "I can't change a tire
我全家都看着我
and my whole family is watching me
我却连这么简单的事都不会
not be able to do something simple."
你真刻薄
You are mean.
-有点过了  鲍勃  -你怎么了  老爸
- Yeah, Bob. - Geez, Dad.
咋了  我们的车发动不了时吐槽的可是他
What? He's the one who said it to us when our car wouldn't start.
-没错  但他很风趣  -他比我风趣
- Yeah, but he was funny. - He was funnier?
-没错  -才没有
- Mm-hmm. Yeah. - No.
-有  -没有
- Yeah. - No.
-不  才不是  -貌似是的
- No, he wasn't. - He kind of was.
你怎么能  好吧  我来帮你  闪开
Are you... all right, let me help. Move over.
-我来帮你  闪开  -他又那样了
- "Let me help. Move over." - He just did it again!
-他又那样了  -他还在学我
- "He just did it again." - He's doing it right now!
他还在学我
"He's doing it right now."
是啊  蛮好玩的
Oh, yeah, it's funny.
肃静
Order.
反对无效
I'll allow it.
罪名成立
Guilty.
无罪释放
Not guilty.
我有裁决结果了
I think I have my ruling.
审判继续
Moving on.
好吧
Right.